Our next protest is Black Friday and here's what we're doing. Number one, we're boycotting all
consumerism. You're not buying anything on Black Friday. We are not spending one red cent on
anything on Black Friday. Number two, we are going to hashtag fight money with money. We are divesting
our money from major corporate banks and putting it into credit unions. Follow the hashtag to learn
more about this movement. And yes, banks are closed on Thanksgiving, but they are open on Black Friday.
Number three, for those of us who are fired up, we are protesting in person. Everyone who is humanly
possible that can get to Washington, D.C. is going to the White House. That means basically anyone on
the eastern seaboard or within driving distance, or if you got money like that, flying distance
to Washington, D.C. is going to show up outside the White House. And for those of us who cannot make
it to Washington, D.C., we are going to our state capital and we are protesting. And if you live in
a huge state like Florida or Texas, where your state capital is like eight hours away and you can't do
that either, then go to your local city mayor's office. We did it for the Women's March. We can do
it for Palestine. And we're doing a social media blackout, posting the Palestine flag. That's it.
Palestine, the flag. That's all you got to do. Post it on your Instagram, post it on your Facebook,
on your Twitter, on your ex, on your TikTok. Let's flood our timelines with our support.
There's nothing that needs to be said at this point. It's been said. We're just showing solidarity
in numbers. If you agree with this plan, like, comment, share. Let's get the ball rolling on social
media so we can take it to the next step, which is start organizing in small groups in real life
so we can all unite to make this happen. And if you don't live in the USA, but you want to join
in in global solidarity, we are referring to Friday, November 24th as an action day.